<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>David Dreggors</title>
    <link>https://ddreggors.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on David Dreggors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>david.dreggors@redhat.com (David Dreggors)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>david.dreggors@redhat.com (David Dreggors)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 13:31:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ddreggors.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Secrets and how to handle them</title>
      <link>https://ddreggors.github.io/posts/its-a-secret/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 13:31:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>david.dreggors@redhat.com (David Dreggors)</author>
      <guid>https://ddreggors.github.io/posts/its-a-secret/</guid>
      <description>Shhhh it&amp;rsquo;s a secret&amp;hellip; There are often times we want to incorporate items like passwords or other sensitive data in our code or repositories. This is generally a bad idea even in provate repos or server filesystems. In fact there are teams of security specialists in most companies that watch for this practice and act rather harshly when identified.
While most of us have done this (even if only at home in our labs or test code), there really shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a reason to do this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonding With OpenShift</title>
      <link>https://ddreggors.github.io/posts/bonding-with-ocp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 21:13:22 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>david.dreggors@redhat.com (David Dreggors)</author>
      <guid>https://ddreggors.github.io/posts/bonding-with-ocp/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes we just want to bond with OpenShift&amp;hellip; David Dreggors david.dreggors@redhat.com 2021-06-06
The issues You may find yourself needing to customize your nodes network devices, this will often mean that you require interfaces (nic) bonding. On a standalone Linux host this is pretty straight forward, however managing your cluster nodes is not as easy as logging in and changing the interfaces. OpenShift handles changes on the nodes via machine configs and the machine config operator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://ddreggors.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 08:49:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>david.dreggors@redhat.com (David Dreggors)</author>
      <guid>https://ddreggors.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello World David Dreggors david.dreggors@redhat.com 2021-05-27
The title, as cliché as it is in the software world, still seems fitting. After all this blog post is my first here and the internet is global, so it is my introduction to the world. Add to that the fact that most projects today start with a Hello World example. So here is mine.
I have spent the better part of my life dedicated to computers (hardware, software, and the use of).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
